hauntedhouse.com 2010-06-21

# HauntedHouse.com Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Protecting privacy is always a Haunt Holdings, LLC priority. To underscore our fundamental commitment to privacy and our vision that good privacy is good business, we have adopted a online privacy policy for our Web site: www.hauntedhouse.com. This policy reflects and implements---in an online setting---our corporate privacy principles and Fair Information Practice Principles of notice, choice, access, security, and accountability. 

This online privacy policy applies to HauntedHouse.comwhich is operated by **Haunt Holdings, LLC**

Haunt Holdings, LLC  
101 Convention Center Drive, Suite 700  
Las Vegas, NV 89109   
Email:[ info@hauntedhouse.com](mailto:info@hauntedhouse.com)

**INFORMATION COLLECTION**

  * Personally-identifiable information. 

This site only collects personally-identifiable information from you if you choose to provide this information to us. Personally-identifiable information collected with your consent may include, for example, name, e-mail address, resume information, or any inquires you may make through our Web site. Haunt Holdings, LLC does not provide personally-identifiable information to unaffiliated third-parties in its normal course of business. However, we will provide such information when required by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to comply with the law or legal process. 

“Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. This site uses third party cookies, however personally identifiable information is not collected through the use of cookies. Cookies are used to determine whether a visitor is unique or whether the visitor has viewed our site before. With the exception of the portion of our site dedicated to applying for employment with Haunt Holdings, LLC, cookies are optional and do not affect the operability of our site. 

While most browsers are set to accept cookies by default, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you before accepting them. Your browser manufacturer has information on changing the default setting for your specific browser. 

  * Non personally-identifiable information. 

This site also collects nonpersonally-identifiable information. For example, as you browse this Web site we may collect information about your visit, but not about you personally. Via web server logs, for example, we may monitor statistics such as: the number of people that visit our site, which page(s) are visited on our site, from which domain our visitors come (e.g., aol.com, hotmail.com, etc.), and which browsers people use to visit our site (e.g., Netscape Navigator, Microsoft Internet Explorer, etc.). Our Web site uses an outsourcing program to assist us in analyzing this data to better tailor our Web site. 

We reserve the right to retain personally-identifiable information collected through this site for the length of our business relationship with you. In some cases, we will retain the information for a longer period if required to do so by law, regulation, or the Individual Reference Services Group Industry Principles. 

INFORMATION USE AND CONSUMER CHOICE. 

The information collected by this Web site is used only for responding to your inquiries and otherwise corresponding with you, for processing transactions you request, maintaining your account (if you have one), and for the administration, review and/or the improvement the content of our Web sites. 

We may contact you in response to your comments or inquiries, as part of the maintenance of your account with us (if you have one), or in order to complete a transaction that you requested. 

If you decide that you do not want to receive further e-mails regarding your inquiry from Haunt Holdings, LLC, you can reply to the e-mail or use the telephone number 708.932.5153 with a request that we not continue to e-mail you. We do not use outside data sources to enrich marketing data obtained online. 

ONWARD TRANSFER. 

We may disclose information you provide to us to third parties in order to complete a transaction that you requested. 

We may also outsource some tasks, including the operation of certain Web site functions, that require access to information you supply online. In such cases, however, we require that the companies acting on our behalf abide by our privacy policy and institute safeguards to protect the confidentiality of your information. 

Finally, please note that we may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to comply with the law or legal process. 

ACCESS AND CORRECTION. 

As an information company, we know the importance of accurate data. Therefore, we strive to maintain the accuracy of the information collected through this Web site. Furthermore, we believe that the individual is invaluable in ensuring that data is complete and accurate. We will provide you with access to personally-identifiable information you provide through our Web site for as long as we maintain that information in a readily accessible format. Similarly, we permit and encourage you to correct inaccuracies in the information you submit to us through our Web site. 

If you wish to correct any inaccurate information you have submitted to this site, please call or send an e-mail to: 

SECURITY. 

We take steps to protect against the loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration of personally-identifiable information collected through this Web site. We recognize the importance of security for all personally-identifiable information collected by our Web site. We exercise care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers. 

Once we receive personally-identifiable information, we take steps to protect its security on our systems. In the event we request or transmit sensitive information, such as credit card information or Social Security Numbers, we use industry standard, secure socket layer ("SSL") encryption. 

We strictly limit access to personally-identifiable information to those employees who need access in order to carry out their job responsibilities. All employees are prohibited from "browsing" through our files and databases. We train our employees in the application of our need-to-know standard. We periodically audit for compliance with this standard and we impose penalties for any failure to comply with this standard. 

POLICY CHANGES. 

We may revise this online privacy policy from time to time. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on the Web site. If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you via e-mail. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post the notice we will also e-mail users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.
